SOLD OUT ON YOU
Do you want perfection?
Then, don't stand by my side.
INSTANT CURRY
Say "Ah."
It's so delicious.
No need to worry about tonight's dinner!
EUNSUNG SUPER VACUUM
-You're a lifesaver.
Mom…
Ye-jin!
Ye-jin, are you okay? Are you hurt?
Mom…
Dad,
this person is my mom, right?
Is it?
Is she really my mom?
Mom!
It's me, Dam Seok-gyeong.
Ye-jin's having a hard time.
Can you meet her just once?
Ye-jin.
It's me, your mom.
Come here.
Mom!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
-How is it? Is it good?
-It's good.
Mom.
Can't we play outside next time?
What?
I want to go
to an amusement park with you.
Well…
-I'm really busy--
-Then…
When can I see you again?
Ye-jin.
This is my number.
You can call me at this number
when you miss me.
Really?
But can you promise me
just one thing in return?
Until I come to see you,
promise to never come looking for me.
Because--
Because it's our secret.
Can I call you every day?
Right, you're busy.
Then, how about this?
Every Sunday night at 8:00 p.m.,
no matter how busy I am,
I promise to pick up.
Hey, Ye-jin.
Mom, I became class president!
Everyone except three people voted for me.
Congratulations!
EUN-SU'S LAW
COMMENT
SONG MYEONG-HWA'S ACTING IS AMAZING!
MOM
Mom, do you finally get
your revenge tomorrow?
Can't you tell just me?
It's more fun if you watch it yourself.
Ms. Song.
They need me.
-Let's talk more next week.
-Okay.
I love you--
The person you are calling is unavailable.
-Gosh, Song Myeong-hwa got in an accident.
-Really? What happened?
SONG MYEONG-HWA
IN CRITICAL CONDITION AFTER CAR CRASH
Correct that false report first.
-Ms. Song Myeong-hwa!
How did the accident occur?
What happened to the others?
Mom!
Do you know this kid?
I mean…
You can't just let anyone in here!
Sorry. She needs to rest right now.
-Please leave right now!
-Song Myeong-hwa!
Mom, I'm sorry.
Please, just pick up.
Mom, please answer the phone.
Just once…
The person you are calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message…
Just once…
Mom.
Why weren't you picking up?
Are you listening?
You've called the wrong number.
Hello?
Mom?
-Mom.
-If you call me one more time,
I'm going to call the cops.
This is my last warning.
-Look here.
-I miss you.
I miss you,
Mom.
SOM'S VARIETY SHOP
Jin-yi!
It seems our regulars
are here early this morning.
Hey, Jin-yi. My stool, please.
-A stool for me too.
-Your stools!
All right.
-A high one for you.
-A high one.
And a low one for you.
Thank you.
Don't share these
just because you're friends, okay?
You need to use the right ones
for your heights to protect your knees.
I want to buy a stool too.
Let me hear Jin-yi nag about my knees.
There's no need to buy one.
-Just give me one.
-Save your money.
She's so considerate.
Jin-yi is a true businesswoman.
"The Cunning Dealer Jin-yi."
-All right, let's go.
-Let's go.
-We have to go now.
-Bye.
-Let's go have some coffee.
-Let's go get coffee.
Hey, Som-yi!
Hang on! Come here.
I don't want to.
Let me see…
All right.
Wear this.
What is this?
It's a Punggi rayon mask
that I got just for you.
It doesn't trap sweat,
and it's very breathable.
It's so soft. Isn't it awesome?
Forget it. I'll stick with what I have.
Five, four, three!
Come on!
What do you think?
It's so-so.
Na Som-yi.
No way!
Jin-yi, this is what I really wanted!
What kind of angel left this here for me?
Who else would it be?
You begged Mechoori for it, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I'm going to open this later,
so keep it safe for me.
You're doing great.
My eyes are a bit puffy.
Did I eat too much soup last night?
Goodness.
Are you leaving?
Yes. Are you heading out too?
-Yeah, I'm going to the market.
-I see.
Let's go together. I'm riding the bus too.
Sure. I'll give you a ride there.
-You drive?
-Of course not.
There's someone who never lets me walk.
Yeah, that's the one!
This chicken was flying
like an eagle yesterday!
You…
You treated me like a thief
and even called the cops.
But is that really a chicken though?
I'm telling you, it's really weird.
You don't have anything to say to me?
Here.
I wasn't asking for repair costs.
An apology--
We're all done, right?
I hope we don't cross paths again.
Excuse me!
What? What is it now?
Let's talk.
We're going to miss the bus! Let's go.
You can't take out any of this stuff?
No. I only have space to give you a ride.
Then, she can sit on my lap.
You got knee surgery last year.
You can't do that.
You should get on, ma'am.
I'll just walk.
Why don't you come with us?
We're going to be late.
My goodness.
Just sit.
You look so good together.
-Darling, do you have a boyfriend?
-Pardon?
Ma'am!
Gosh, my knees hurt. I better sit down.
Put your feet up.
Okay.
Oh, my gosh!
Bees! Mister, there are bees over here!
Are they gone yet?
Are they gone?
They're gone.
Why were they all over me?
That's what I wanted to ask.
I'm sorry
about yesterday's misunderstanding.
I was too harsh.
Well…
I totally get it.
Let's call it even.
The envelope of money!
I put it in the corner of your trailer,
so don't forget it.
I don't need it.
I don't need it either.
You said it was expensive.
Please…
Hey, I'm Dam Ye-jin.
Dam Ye-jin?
Hurry up.
Ma'am, you can just pay later
when you get off.
-It's not that…
-Geez.
Aren't you hungry?
I bet you didn't have any breakfast.
Eat this.
It must be tough.
Sang-geum, why would you give
that grumpy man any food?
WE SPENT OUR TWENTIES TOGETHER
Hey, Ae-ra!
We met when we were eight,
but now we're 40.
Forty!
We're "Young Forty"!
Hey, Ae-ra.
My next NeoTube video
is going to be called
"Introducing Hidden Gems in our Town."
And of course,
we can't be leaving you out.
You were our student president,
valedictorian,
and leader of the kids
in our neighborhood.
Don't you have anything to do?
I'll film a great clip of you
at that macaron place.
What do you say?
Come on. What do you say?
How many subscribers did you say you have?
Seven…
subscribers.
Will you do it if I get ten?
-Are you crazy?
-Fifteen?
-That's enough.
-Twenty?
Born and raised in Deokpung,
I'm Deokpung rep Park Kwang-mo,
and I'm here today to introduce
these plastic bottle pinwheels.
It's a budget-friendly mole repellent.
When the wind blows,
these bottles spin around,
and the vibrations go underground.
The moles think
it's an earthquake and run off.
It's very budget-friendly
and easy to install--
What's that?
Right as I speak,
here comes our village's true gem.
It's Mechoori.
He's coming.
He's still coming.
He should stop coming now.
To all the fans of Park Kwang-mo TV--
Hey!
Hey, Mechoori!
You can't be drowsy driving
around the rice paddies.
I didn't get enough sleep.
Why? Was there a mosquito?
It was something
more persistent than a mosquito.
What?
What are you saying?
Mom?
Mom…
Mom.
Just go and get some rest today.
I'll take care of the farm.
All right. I'd appreciate that.
Sure.
What is that?
What?
Mechoori, what's that?
-Please do it as fast as you can.
-Yes, sir.
Mu-won, come on out.
Hey.
You're home.
Explain this.
Explain what?
Didn't you see?
They're doing construction.
We're building your lab.
Without even asking me? What is this?
You're the one who changed your number.
I was going to tell you in advance.
I wanted to get it done
while you were at the farm.
I told you I won't do it.
Are you just going to farm here forever?
Is this really the life you wanted?
-Yes.
-No.
You're the happiest when you're in a lab.
-We did it!
-We actually did it!
Finally!
Chang-ho made it big in Bangkok.
He said business suits him
way better than research.
But what about you?
How long are you going to live like this?
I told you.
-I like the way things are now.
-Just wait.
That lab is going to produce
a game changer that will rock Korea.
Sir!
Why can't you understand
what I'm saying? Hey!
Sir… Excuse me!
Yes?
Could you stop for a bit?
How about a break?
-Pardon?
-Take a break.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Let's take a break.
I seriously can't believe you.
Do you know how many calls
I got from L'Étoile today?
They call nonstop--
L'ÉTOILE CHA JOONG-HOON
It's driving me crazy too.
Meet them again and make it clear
that we won't renew the contract.
You tell them.
If you're half as cold to them
as you are to me, they'll give up.
You do it.
What are you… Hey.
Hello?
Why haven't you left yet?
-I'm leaving now.
-Yes, please go.
Gosh, you scared me.
Hey,
you still don't know who I am?
I'm Kang Mu-won.
Kang Mu-won!
I can't let you go looking like this.
All done.
Why didn't you show me
a perfect suit like this?
It's the same suit
you are wearing.
What?
You're killing it.
Stop!
Please, stop!
Yes, could we please stop now?
I told you there's no need.
-Just take it, will you?
-Mu-won.
Can't I just take a taxi?
Listen. All these little details
are needed to gain the upper hand.
No matter how well you fight,
you can't win a war without weapons…
I'm going to be late.
Hey, wear this instead.
Mu-won.
All right, fine. Then, just take the car.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Gojeuneok Bio's co-CEO, Lee Hae-seok.
I'm Eric Seo from L'Étoile.
I admit that last time,
our order quantity
of raw materials was unreasonable.
This is a revised contract
with the condition
that the raw material supply
will increase gradually.
To increase raw material production,
it also says we will be covering
facility expansion costs and labor costs.
It seems you still don't
fully understand why we won't re-sign.
Gojeuneok's first rule
is for me to have full control
over the entire process.
We cannot continue with a company
that breaks this rule.
With proper facilities and personnel,
I'm sure it will be manageable.
Those things alone can't guarantee
the quality of the materials.
Don't you want more people
to use better quality essence?
That intention may become a mistake.
No, it will become hope.
Hope can help us get started,
but it can't take responsibility
for the outcome.
That reckless optimism
is exactly why we can't work together.
Then, what if we take the same quantity
as our previous contract?
I heard you're preparing to launch on HIT.
We're only selling a limited amount.
I'm sure they'll request
a bigger quantity for the next broadcast.
There's no reason to continue working
with a company that backtracks…
on prior agreements.
I believe I've made myself clear,
so I'll head out.
You sure you won't regret it?
This is L'Étoile.
Maybe I shouldn't have said
that last line.
What did you need to tell me so urgently?
I had something to share.
Gojeuneok Bio has co-CEOs.
Kang Mu-won and Lee Hae-seok.
Lee Hae-seok?
Lee Hae-seok has control
over deciding the contract renewal,
but he's quite firm in his stance.
You met him?
Where is he right now?
He's not someone who's that easy to meet.
Him too?
It's the same with the farm owner.
I failed to meet him so many times.
It seems
people who are very similar to each other
work at Gojeuneok Bio.
Let's go with Plan B now.
If there are two of them,
we need to match their numbers.
I'll try and convince
Mr. Lee Hae-seok from now on.
Mr. Seo?
You really don't recognize me?
You really don't remember me?
I do.
You remember me?
But why did you pretend not to?
Because I felt so sorry.
I felt bad I couldn't be there that day.
You mean
you wanted to come
but you couldn't, right?
Did something happen that day?
Well, it was a long time ago.
Then, how about we chat like back then
until you can remember?
Mr. Seo.
All right. Let's focus on Plan B.
Can't we just find
a different raw material producer?
I talked to headquarters about that too.
But apparently, they tried to farm
white flower noori mushrooms in France
and failed.
And even if they had succeeded,
the process of extracting the ingredients
is Gojeuneok's exclusive technology.
Then, the conclusion is
that they're the only choice.
What did the farm owner say?
Don't get me started.
I didn't even get to meet him.
The workers on the farm there
say he's really strict.
And he seems to hate
communicating with outsiders.
These two people…
They're virtually doppelgängers.
STRICT, DIFFICULT TO REACH
Maybe the same guy?
Mr. Hwang!
-Right?
-What do we do with him?
-That was his best?
-No way.
-That was lame.
-Fire him.
I mean, we can't say it's impossible…
Look.
How can someone manage
the company and the farm at the same time?
Do you think he can just teleport
back and forth?
It's tough to even manage one job,
you know.
I'm having such a hard time right now.
ANYOUNG RICE
Yes.
Anyway, please call me
if there's anything available.
Come on. Weekends don't matter.
I need the money.
Yes. All right, bye.
Use this for baby formula.
Honey?
Hey, it's me.
-Why aren't you coming inside?
-It's nothing. Go on in.
Hey, did you order rice?
Hey, Se-jung. How was your day?
PROUD AND CONFIDENT, DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
I'm sorry for everything.
I…
I was struggling to get by,
and it made me struggle to be generous.
I thought I was all alone in this world
and did a lot of things I was ashamed of.
From now on, I'll stick
to the precise schedule
and I won't speed.
You can tell me whenever you need
to use the restroom before we leave.
Thank you so much!
-Thank you!
Just think of this
as saving someone's life.
Please help me out just this once.
Ma'am, I'm telling you
I'm really busy right now.
We get the most views
when you appear on our channel!
Hello, HIT subscribers!
I'm home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
Today, I'll be trying out a day
as a call center agent
to personally hear
the kind of difficulties
our customers actually may have.
All right, shall we go?
Hello, this is--
That shampoo you're selling now…
I only want to buy half of Set 1,
so give me a 50% discount.
Ma'am, I'm really sorry,
but I'm not authorized
to adjust the set or the price.
Wait, you want me to buy something
I can't even use all of?
Are you encouraging
unnecessary consumption?
Hello, how may I help you?
Well, I want to return
the short rib soup I bought.
Was there anything wrong
with the soup you ordered?
I ate it, but it wasn't to my taste.
So you sampled one pack,
but it wasn't to your--
No.
I ate all of them,
but they didn't taste good,
and the bones were too big.
They were so heavy.
You ate everything,
so how can you return--
I said I ate everything!
I didn't leave any!
-Hello--
-You better fix this.
Pardon?
How may I help you, sir?
My family has fallen apart
because of these damn golf shoes.
You ordered
white women's golf shoes in size 235.
Why would you send them
the next morning after my order?
My wife saw these!
-Pardon?
-Forget it.
My wife's filing for divorce,
and I'm going to be bleeding money
with alimony and everything,
so you better compensate me
for emotional distress.
Is he out of his damn…
I can't believe these people.
Excuse me, Ms. Dam?
Could you please just take
one call smoothly?
Sorry.
I'll do a proper call this time.
I will now be a yes-man.
-Yes-man.
That's right.
Yes! Yes!
And there's a call right on time.
Let's get into it.
Hello, this is Dam Ye-jin,
your agent for today--
-Is this HIT?
-Yes, it is.
How can you sell
a ridiculous item like this?
Is there something wrong
with the item you purchased?
Don't you have a quality control team?
You shipped out something
that doesn't even work properly.
This is how you handle things?
You're using that
as a drying rack for laundry?
No matter how long I sit in there,
I don't sweat at all.
Is it broken?
This was so expensive.
Gosh, it's giving me a headache.
Whatever's wrong with it,
it's just an expensive wooden chair now.
I see.
You trusted home shopping host
Dam Ye-jin and bought it,
-but there was an issue--
-I've never trusted Dam Ye-jin.
I'm very disappointed though.
I see.
Please wait one moment.
Excuse me, sir,
but could you tell me your name
so I can check your purchase information?
It's Lee Hae-seok.
DEOKPUNG VILLAGE
Gojeuneok Bio has co-CEOs.
Kang Mu-won and Lee Hae-seok.
These two people…
They're virtually doppelgängers.
Maybe the same guy?
Him too?
It's the same with the farm owner.
I failed to meet him so many times.
Mr. "Lee something Seok"? Mr. Lee!
For privacy reasons,
the middle character is hidden.
-What's your full name?
-It's Matthew.
Gojeuneok Bio has co-CEOs.
The farm owner… "Lee something Seok"…
It's Lee Hae-seok.
FARM OWNER
LEE HAE-SEOK
It's Lee Hae-seok.
Sir, can you wait just one moment?
Tell him the staff in charge
will come in person to take care of it.
Seriously, thank you so much.
Thank you!
Hit or push through my car if you want.
No!
I've had men follow me in their sports
cars before, but a tractor is a first.
It's pretty unique.
I guess "Mechoori" means Matthew Lee,
not "mechoori" as in quail.
That jerk.
Ye-jin! You must've lost your mind!
I must've been crazy!
Wait. I can make it up to him.
Can I?
I can.
I don't think I can.
No, I have to.
I have to.
I must.
I can do it.
Right.
Let's give it a try.
Hello!
It's nice to see you again.
Did you forget the agreement?
I'm here today because you called me.
I'm your call center agent.
Just give me the number
for the staff in charge.
HIT
DAM YE-JIN
-Are you kidding me?
-What?
I sold the products,
so I'm the staff in charge.
Where's your bathtub, sir?
Fine. Go take a look,
Ms. Dam.
Yes, sir! I'll make my way in!
I ran a detailed inspection,
and it's not broken.
It was just operator error, sir.
This blanket
will be included for preheating.
Cover the top with this blanket,
turn the power on, and wait 20 minutes.
Please keep this in mind.
I explained
that you have to cover it
with this blanket to preheat it.
I emphasized it several times,
but I guess you didn't listen.
You can't just insist it's working.
"Insist"?
Then, did you think
we sent this blanket
as a meaningless freebie?
Are you embarrassed because you complained
that a perfectly fine machine was broken?
Seriously?
It doesn't make you sweat!
There's no need to explain.
I'll just show you
whether you sweat or not.
Open that too.
Don't file another complaint later
saying that's broken too.
Fine. We'll open that too.
It's already hot and steamy
with the preheating, isn't it?
It's not nearly hot enough to sweat.
You better hope so.
Hold on a minute.
What are you doing?
What?
You're pressing pressure points
that help you sweat.
You think those tricks will fool me?
If massaging your temples caused sweat,
all saunas would disappear.
I work on little sleep and suffer
from headaches due to such bias.
You're sweating!
See? You're sweating! Right there!
The ceiling's leaking.
The ceiling? Why?
It looks completely fine.
Mr. Mechoori, look here.
Look here, not the ceiling.
Mr. Mechoori!
You see all this sweat forming here?
My house is usually hot.
Raise your arms.
-What?
-Raise your arms.
Why?
What?
-Mr. Mechoori, let me see your arms.
-Why?
Come on. I need to check something.
-Check what?
-Just raise them once.
-For what?
-Just one minute.
-Go away.
-It's over for you.
-I got you. Raise your arms.
-Hey, what are you…
Sit. Raise your arms.
Ms. Dam!
Tickle, tickle!
-What?
-Wait…
Okay, fine!
-I take back my complaint!
-No, it's too late.
-I need to see--
-Ms. Dam!
TEMPERATURE
ERROR
I guess you were a bit embarrassed,
seeing how you even gave me tea.
If you're not going to drink it, then go.
Our business is over.
How long are you going to
keep playing dumb for?
You think I came all the way here
just to check on the product?
Don't look down on HIT's QC team.
You're the one who overreacted.
I simply made a call
to the service center.
That's what I mean.
Don't you get why I overreacted?
Let me formally introduce myself,
Mr. Lee Hae-seok.
I'll see you again, Mr. Lee!
Changsik.
Changsik!
Hey, Changsik.
Are you ignoring me too?
Give me your paw.
Hey, I'm feeling really down today.
Come on.
Just once, Changsik.
Give me your paw!
Hey, come on. Give me your paw.
Hey.
-Ma'am.
-Give this to him.
Hey, whether it's a dog or a human,
they say you should feed them
before telling them what to do.
If you want him to listen to you,
you need to feed him first.
Right.
I need to feed him first.
Changsik, here.
What would he like then?
That's right! Your bathtub, ma'am.
I got a call from Mechoori.
He said it's fine.
You came all the way here for nothing.
It's fine. I came for other reasons too.
And I was missing your potatoes.
You want some potatoes before you go?
Ma'am, if you keep asking me
to stay overnight like this…
Sure!
FARMING LOG
Are you up?
Yes. Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to the mushroom farm.
They're short-handed.
-Where?
-The mushroom farm.
Did you sleep well?
The weather's so nice.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Good morning.
-Hey.
-Good morning. Did you sleep well?
-Yes.
Ms. Dam?
How did you know?
Well,
I guess farming clothes
can't hide my beauty.
Right…
This is my last warning.
Please, just leave.
Sweetie, come here!
Yes, ma'am!
She's calling me.
Wait…
I'm coming!
Deokpung's pride and treasure,
the white flower noori mushrooms!
As always,
please handle each one with care!
Come on!
Let's go!
-Let's go!
We're getting off work right on the dot.
-That's right!
-On the dot!
Our work is not over yet!
Deokpung's--
Let's go!
Make sure to wrap up for us!
See you!
Good work today.
Right.
I'm going through all this effort,
so could you please spare me some time?
Did you review the materials I left you?
No.
Then, just give me ten… No, five minutes.
Give me five minutes, and I'll brief you.
It's fine.
Can't you reconsider
and renew the contract?
L'Étoile said they'll just accept
the quantity you can produce,
so there's no issue now.
They already broke our trust.
We can't work with people
who have already broken their promise.
Are you a robot or something?
Business is done by people.
It can't be perfect all the time.
Ms. Dam.
Can you put spilled milk
back in the glass?
Look, I'm saying
we can quickly wipe it with a towel.
And if we dry it in the sun
and squeeze it out, we can reuse it.
If it's not dried properly,
it'll get moldy.
That's what we call contamination.
All right?
I understand what you're saying,
but if you could just reconsider…
I'm practically pleading, sir. Please?
If we discuss this further,
you might change your mind…
My hand!
My hand was almost caught in the gate.
If you take one step inside,
I'll immediately call the police.
Ms. Dam!
Hey, we even did a sauna session together.
You're so mean.
Will you please leave?
I will but…
What are you doing?
-I'll leave, but if we could talk…
-Hey…
-You're using force?
-You're the one pushing right now.
Just a moment. Please, sir.
-Ms. Dam!
-Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee!
"IN"
CHARACTER FOR "PERSON"
DERIVED FROM PEOPLE
LEANING ON EACH OTHER
Please get off me.
No, don't come in. Get out.
I'm going to!
For crying out loud.
Ms. Dam?
Hang on…
I do understand your decision, Mr. Lee.
But that makes me want this more.
I really want to introduce an essence
made with good ingredients
to our customers.
Gosh, talking all by myself
is making my mouth hurt.
Oh, dear.
Give it a rest.
It really hurts.
What if it's broken forever?
It's hurting so much.
Okay, it's all done.
It's not good if it gets wet,
so be careful.
Is it okay to take this off
just for a moment this evening?
Sorry?
WOORI DEOKPUNG MEDICAL CLINIC
Why did you have to fall
so dramatically like that?
Were you trying
to blackmail me with an injury?
If I was going to use such tacky methods,
I would've used my beauty first.
So,
should I change my tactics then?
I have a live broadcast at 11:00 p.m.
I can't let my injury stand out
more than the product.
I've prepared so hard for that item too.
It's this way.
I have a live broadcast at 11:00 p.m.
I can't let my injury stand out
more than the product.
HIT
If you look here,
you can adjust the resistance.
Whether beginner or expert,
you can tailor your workout
to match your fitness level.
After you adjust it,
grab the bar,
pull it all the way back, and that's it.
You'll get both cardio
and strength training in one go.
Then, push all the way out with your legs.
You have to pull the bar all the way back
toward your upper abdomen
to maximize your workout.
That must hurt…
It really feels like
you're rowing on water.
There's strong resistance when you pull.
That makes me want this more.
I really want to introduce an essence
made with good ingredients
to our customers.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
DAM YE-JIN
Jin-yi.
What are you doing here at this hour--
You're such a negligent landlord.
Your tenant wasn't paying rent,
but you didn't press them.
I said you didn't have to.
And I told you hundreds of times
I refuse to be treated
like a charity case.
What about Som-yi?
She's busy bragging about the gift
that someone left her.
What was she doing here?
It's nothing.
Nothing?
Hey.
What is it this time?
The Beauty Song essence that Ms. Song's
been preparing for three years…
It's launching soon.
Customers won't buy essence again
a week after buying L'Étoile's essence.
They will if it's good.
You should be focusing
on the product's quality.
Are you really that bent
on dragging Ms. Song down?
Poor Ms. Song.
You really are cruel. Geez.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
DAM YE-JIN
Mu-won, let's end things
with L'Étoile for good.
Send me the list of other clients.
PERILLA LEAVES, BELLFLOWER ROOT,
MEAT PATTIES, STUFFED CUCUMBER KIMCHI
YOU MUST BE BUSY
Welcome back.
Did you eat dinner yet?
I don't have an appetite.
You haven't eaten, have you?
-Come here, I'll make you--
-Please, just…
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
It's nothing.
What about dinner?
Geez.
Can't you stop nagging me about my meals?
I told you a million times I can't eat.
I don't have the time!
Why do you keep giving me food
that I'll end up throwing away?
It just makes me feel bad.
It's okay if you throw them all away.
I just don't want your fridge to be empty
when you want to eat something.
Geez…
You shouldn't just barge in here, Dad.
I'm not a kid.
I told you,
I don't need stuff like this right now!
Why do you always…
just do as you please?
Ye-jin.
Please, don't do this.
But it's true.
Mom abandoned me.
-Ye-jin.
-I don't care anymore.
I'm going to tell everyone.
I'm going to tell them
Song Myeong-hwa's my mom
and that she's a liar.
I told her not to contact you!
What?
Your mom actually did call.
She said she was so startled then,
and she wanted to apologize to you.
But,
I can't…
see you get hurt like that again.
So I told her not to contact you again.
I'm the one who stopped her.
Why?
Why did you do that?
What about me?
Why decide that on your own?
Who are you to stop her?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
GOJEUNEOK BIO
Hello?
Mom.
Excuse me.
-I clearly told you--
-It's me, Ye-jin.
What?
Who did you say you were?
Did you see my show?
Actually, I got hurt today.
3 MISSED CALLS
Whenever I moved,
it hurt so much,
so I just didn't care…
and wanted to quit the show.
But I held it in.
Didn't I do a good job, Mom?
I'm a pro, aren't I?
Ms. Dam.
Are you drunk?
But…
today…
I guess I was pretty stressed.
I took my anger out on Dad for no reason.
Hang up before you embarrass yourself.
I'm pathetic,
aren't I?
I'm hanging up.
Hello?
Ms. Dam!
The person you are calling is unavailable.
Mom…
I miss you,
Mom.
I'm bleeding.
SCHOOL ZONE
CONVENIENCE STORE
SOLD OUT ON YOU
THANKS TO SPECIAL GUEST AHN SANG-WOO
Are you curious whether she slept well
or if she made sure to eat her meals?
Are talks going smoothly
with Gojeuneok Bio?
It's been a long time, Mr. Lee.
Whatever you do,
nothing's going to change.
He won't buy the corn?
All this corn might go to waste.
This has nothing to do with you.
-Let's sell them.
-What?
Let's sell them through a livestream.
Hello, everyone.
I'm home shopping host Dam Ye-jin.
Ms. Dam, stay still.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park